FIRST 'The Land That Time Forgot'. THEN 'At The Earth's Core'. NOW
a fantastic incredible world of savage mystery...
The People That Time Forgot is a adventure, fantasy,
science fiction film directed by Kevin Connor.
Major Ben McBride organizes a mission to the Antarctic wastes to search for his
friend who has been missing in the region for several years.
McBride's party find themselves in a world populated by primitive warriors and terrifying
prehistoric creatures, all of whom they must evade in order to get back safely
Ben McBride, played by Patrick Wayne.
Bowen Tyler, played by Doug McClure.
Charly, played by Sarah Douglas.
Ajor, played by Dana Gillespie.
Norfolk, played by Thorley Walters.
Hogan, played by Shane Rimmer.
The People That Time Forgot is a 1977 adventure fantasy film based on the novel The People
That Time Forgot (1963) and Out of Time's Abyss (1963) by Edgar Rice Burroughs.
Filmed in Technicolor, it was produced by Britain's Amicus
Productions and directed by Kevin Connor.
Like Connor's other two Burroughs-derived films, The Land That Time Forgot and At the Earth's Core,
the film was distributed in the United States by American International Pictures.
It is the last film made by Amicus before the production company folded.
The film is a direct sequel to The Land That Time
Forgot, which initiated the series in 1974.
The story follows a rescue expedition, led by Patrick Wayne in search of his
friend, played by Doug McClure, who had vanished many years before.
The expedition lands on Caprona, the same fantastic prehistoric land
where dinosaurs and barbarian tribes of men co-exist.
The film explores themes of rescue, ship, island,
monster, based on novel or book.
The tone is thought_provoking.